So let's just run through it really quick up to the point where we decide what to eat.
所以让我们快速浏览一下，直到我们决定吃什么。
All right.
好的。
Hello.
你好。
Hey.
嘿。
Hey Luke.
嘿，卢克。
Hey how's it going.
嘿，进展如何。
It's going all right.
一切顺利。
You.
你。
Yeah.
是的。
Going pretty well just sitting around at home eating some snacks.
只是坐在家里吃点零食，过得很好。
OK.
好的。
Cool.
凉爽的。
How are you.
你好吗。
You're free to talk.
你可以自由交谈。
Yeah yeah.
是啊。
Free to talk.
自由交谈。
What's up.
这是怎么回事。
Well I was thinking of going to grab some dinner tonight.
好吧，我想今晚去吃点晚饭。
Would you like to come along yeah.
你愿意一起来吗？
Sounds great.
听起来很棒。
What time.
什么时候。
How about How about seven.
怎么样，七点怎么样。
Seven work for you.
七为你工作。
Actually at 7:00 I need to go pick up my friend from the airport.
实际上在 7:00 我需要去机场接我的朋友。
Could we move it to 8:00.
我们可以把它移到 8:00。
Yeah sure.
好，当然。
8:00 works 8:00 works.
8:00 工作 8:00 工作。
All right.
好的。
8:00 sounds great.
8:00 听起来不错。
What did you have in mind.
你有什么想法。
Or we could say what were you thinking of having.
或者我们可以说你想拥有什么。
What were you thinking of eating.
你想吃什么。
What kind of thing would you like to eat.
你想吃什么样的东西。
Basically these expressions.
基本上就是这些表达。
What did you have in mind.
你有什么想法。
Did you can say Do you have in mind.
你能说你心里有没有。
But we often say did because it makes it sound a little softer or we say What were you thinking of eating
但是我们经常说这样做是因为它听起来更柔和，或者我们说你想吃什么
or having.
或拥有。
It's a very strange have I know but you'll get used to it.
我知道这很奇怪，但你会习惯的。
What were you thinking of having.
你想拥有什么。
These are very very very common or what are you in the mood for if you invite me and then I say to you
这些是非常非常非常常见的，或者如果你邀请我然后我对你说，你有什么心情
OK.
好的。
Yeah sounds great.
是的，听起来很棒。
I'd love to go.
我想去。
What were you thinking of having and you go oh I don't know you haven't thought about where to eat right.
你在想什么，然后你就走了哦，我不知道你还没有想过去哪里吃饭。
So then maybe you need to say to me What are you in the mood for.
那么也许你需要对我说你有什么心情。
You're inviting me.
你在邀请我。
Why are you asking me what.
为什么问我什么。
I'm in the mood for that means what do I feel like eating.
我有心情，因为这意味着我想吃什么。
What do I want to eat.
我想吃什么。
All right.
好的。
That's fine.
没关系。
Then I say you're inviting me but I'm deciding where we eat.
然后我说你在邀请我，但我正在决定我们在哪里吃饭。
Ok then I say How about.
好的，那我说怎么样。
So the way we suggest things often is to use.
所以我们建议事物的方式经常是使用。
How about
怎么样
OK.
好的。
How about Thai food.
泰国菜怎么样。
I know a great Thai restaurant.
我知道一家很棒的泰国餐厅。
But you the person inviting me you had Thai food for lunch just to be clear that's Thai.
但是你邀请我的人午餐吃泰国菜只是为了清楚这是泰国菜。
Thai is the adjective for Thailand the adjective is shorter than the name of the country.
Thai是Thailand的形容词，形容词比国家名称短。
So Thai food.
所以泰国菜。
How about How about Thai food.
泰国菜怎么样。
I know a great Thai restaurant.
我知道一家很棒的泰国餐厅。
Actually it's near your house.
其实它就在你家附近。
Actually I'm not really in the mood.
其实我真的没心情。
We often start sentences this way.
我们经常以这种方式开始句子。
Actually I'm not really in the mood for Thai.
其实我不是很喜欢泰语。
We don't have to say food after every type of food every type of cuisine.
我们不必在每种食物每种美食之后都说食物。
I'm not really in the mood for Thai because actually I had it for lunch.
我对泰语不太感兴趣，因为实际上我午餐吃了它。
I just had it for lunch just means very recently.
我刚吃午饭就意味着最近。
Oh OK well what are you in the mood for.
哦，好吧，你有什么心情。
Now I'm asking you you're the person who's asking me first where I'd like to go.
现在我问你，你是第一个问我想去哪里的人。
What do you feel like eating.
吃什么感觉。
Now maybe you have a friend who knows a good place.
现在也许你有一个朋友知道一个好地方。
My friend told me about a really good sushi restaurant.
我的朋友告诉我一家非常好的寿司店。
I've never been there.
我从来没有去过那里。
That's USA Chai.
那是美国柴。
My friend told me about a really good sushi restaurant.
我的朋友告诉我一家非常好的寿司店。
I've never been there.
我从来没有去过那里。
How about that.
那个怎么样。
Yeah.
是的。
Sounds great.
听起来很棒。
That's great.
那太棒了。
You should have said that the first time right.
你应该第一次说是对的。
Because you're inviting me and you asked me what I felt like eating.
因为你邀请我，你问我想吃什么。
I told you and you said no because you had it for lunch.
我告诉过你，你说不，因为你吃午饭了。
So now it's back to you.
所以现在它还给你。
And now you tell me about a place your friend told you about OK.
现在你告诉我你朋友告诉你的一个地方，OK。
Or have you ever been to and then maybe places called Sushi sushi.
或者你曾经去过然后可能叫寿司寿司的地方。
That's a good name for a sushi restaurant.
这是寿司店的好名字。
If you were been to sushi Sushi.
如果你去过寿司寿司。
Oh I've never been there.
哦，我从来没有去过那里。
It's good.
很好。
Yeah it's great.
是的，这很棒。
It's fantastic.
这是梦幻般的。
It's the best the best sushi in the city.
这是这个城市最好的寿司。
All right.
好的。
Sounds good.
听起来不错。
Sounds great.
听起来很棒。
Again we can use that same expression to say yes.
同样，我们可以使用相同的表达方式说“是”。
All right.
好的。
So when we want to say no we say I don't really feel like it I'm not in the mood for it.
所以当我们想说不时，我们说我真的不喜欢它，我没有心情。
We want to say yes we say.
我们想说是的，我们说。
Sounds great.
听起来很棒。
OK.
好的。
Have you ever been to have you ever been to have you ever had.
你曾经有过你曾经有过你曾经有过。
Just to be clear these are separate.
只是要清楚这些是分开的。
Have you ever had if you say Have you ever had then maybe we won't say the name of the restaurant.
你有没有如果你说你有没有然后也许我们不会说餐厅的名字。
Maybe we'll say the type of food.
也许我们会说食物的类型。
Have you ever had Ethiopian food.
你吃过埃塞俄比亚菜吗？
Oh it's amazing.
哦，太神奇了。
No I haven't.
不，我没有。
I know a really good Ethiopian restaurant.
我知道一家非常好的埃塞俄比亚餐厅。
How about that.
那个怎么样。
Sounds great.
听起来很棒。
Yeah.
是的。
Let's go.
我们走吧。
So in this lesson we've talked about everything you need to know when you want to invite people to do
所以在本课中，我们已经讨论了当你想邀请别人做的时候你需要知道的一切
things.
事物。
We're using food in this case.
在这种情况下，我们使用食物。
We talked about how to do small talk how to make sure other people are free how to ask people why they're
我们讨论了如何进行闲聊如何确保其他人自由如何询问人们为什么
calling us how to actually invite in a casual and natural way.
叫我们如何以一种随意自然的方式实际邀请。
Lots of phrases for that how to say no politely how to say yes politely and show different levels of
很多短语如何礼貌地说不如何礼貌地说是并显示不同程度的
excitement and also how to decide where to eat how to get other people's suggestions and how to give
兴奋以及如何决定在哪里吃饭如何获得别人的建议以及如何给予
our own suggestions even if we haven't been there.
我们自己的建议，即使我们没有去过那里。
Now at the end of the call all you have to do is confirm the person who is inviting the person who is
现在，在通话结束时，您所要做的就是确认正在邀请的人
asking the other person to go out for dinner that person is the one who should confirm at the end of
要求对方出去吃饭，那个人是应该在结束时确认的人
the call to do that.
呼吁这样做。
All they have to do is start with.
他们所要做的就是开始。
So any time you want to confirm information just to make sure you say so.
所以任何时候你想确认信息只是为了确保你这么说。
So it's pretty simple.
所以这很简单。
All you do is say everything that you talked about until now.
你所做的就是说出你到目前为止所说的一切。
So I'll see you I'll see you at Sushi sushi at 8:00 p.m..
所以我会见到你的，我会在晚上 8:00 在 Sushi sushi 见到你。
I'll I'll text you the address.
我会发短信给你地址。
Texts can be a verb here.
文本在这里可以是动词。
That means send it as a text message.
这意味着将其作为短信发送。
I'll see you.
我会见到你的。
So I'll see you at Sushi sushi at 8:00 p.m..
所以晚上 8:00 在 Sushi sushi 见。
I'll text you the address then I say all I have to say is great.
我会把地址发短信给你，然后我说我要说的很好。
Great.
伟大的。
Can't wait.
等不及了。
See you then.
回头见。
Great.
伟大的。
Can't wait.
等不及了。
See you then.
回头见。
All right.
好的。
So this is how we invite people.
所以这就是我们邀请人们的方式。
This is how we say things politely in this kind of situation.
这就是我们在这种情况下礼貌地说话的方式。
It's important to remember that the phrases we learned today are not the only phrases there are many
重要的是要记住，我们今天学到的短语并不是唯一的短语，还有很多
more.
更多的。
And you can do variations of these kind of mix them together in many cases.
在许多情况下，您可以将这些变体混合在一起。
There are many many possibilities more than we could ever cover in even a whole course.
甚至在整个课程中，我们都无法涵盖许多可能性。
All right.
好的。
So to practice this recorded dialogue get your phone out and turn on the record function.
因此，要练习这个录制的对话，请拿出手机并打开录音功能。
Record yourself recording is a great way to actually practice because you have to listen to it and you'll
给自己录音 录音是一种很好的实际练习方式，因为你必须听它，你会
hear some mistakes and you'll catch yourself and get used to self-correcting.
听到一些错误，你会发现自己并习惯于自我纠正。
So record yourself recorded dialogue between two friend.
所以录制自己录制的两个朋友之间的对话。
You need to play both people.
你需要玩两个人。
Right.
正确的。
Don't be embarrassed because you're you're in a room by yourself.
不要因为你自己在一个房间里而感到尴尬。
Just try it and you might have fun with it.
试试吧，你可能会玩得开心。
And if you do try it again try to do it two or three different ways.
如果您再次尝试，请尝试两种或三种不同的方式。
Try to use as many of the expressions that we learned in this lesson as you can and again have fun with
尝试尽可能多地使用我们在本课中学到的表达方式，并再次从中获得乐趣
it.
它。
This is basically all of the general stuff you need to know in the invitation situation.
这基本上是您在邀请情况下需要了解的所有一般内容。
So good luck.
祝你好运。